새벽 네 시 모니터 하나 켜놓고
At 4 AM, with one monitor turned on,
줄줄이 코드를 써 내려가
I write down lines of code.
에러 백 개쯤 지우고 나면
After deleting about a hundred errors,
캐릭터 하나가 눈을 떠
A character opens its eyes.
아무도 모르는 이 작은 세계
This small world, known to no one,
내 손끝에서 태어나는 중
Is being born from my fingertips.
픽셀 속의 꿈을 만들어가
I create dreams within the pixels,
한 칸 한 칸 점프해 올라가
Jumping up, one square at a time.
버그투성이 밤을 건너서
Crossing through the buggy night,
나만의 게임이 시작돼
My own game begins.
스프라이트 하나 그려 넣으면
When I draw in a single sprite,
작은 세상이 움직이잖아
The small world starts to move.
혼자서 다 해야 하는 밤이
The night when I have to do everything by myself
오히려 나를 웃게 만들어
Rather makes me smile.
완성 버튼을 누르는 그날
On the day I press the complete button,
온 세상이 플레이하게 될 거야
The whole world will play it.
픽셀 속의 꿈을 만들어가
I create dreams within the pixels,
한 칸 한 칸 점프해 올라가
Jumping up, one square at a time.
버그투성이 밤을 건너서
Crossing through the buggy night,
나만의 게임이 시작돼
My own game begins.
픽셀 속의 꿈을 만들어가
I create dreams within the pixels,
한 칸 한 칸 점프해 올라가
Jumping up, one square at a time.
언젠가 누군가 플레이할 때
Someday, when someone plays it,
이 밤의 코드가 빛이 돼
The code of this night will become light.